ANDREW JORNITZ

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER



PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer with 28 years of experience in investigations, leadership development, and real-time action planning. Demonstrates a strong ability to enhance operational efficiency. Excited about leveraging a unique blend of skills to innovate and optimize web development processes.

SKILLS

Incident investigation

••••

Leadership development

••••

Real-time action planning

••••

Operational efficiency

••••

Audit program development

••••

Risk management

••••

Security compliance

••••

HTML & CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript

••000

React, Redux, angular JS, Bootstrap, jQuery

••000

React Native & React.Js

••000

Node.is & Express

••000

JSON, RESTful, Postman

••000

MongoDB, PostgreSQL

••000

Web Development

••000

Frontend Frameworks

••000

Backend Development

••000

Database Management

••000

API Development

• • 0 0 0

UI/UX Design

 $\bullet \bullet \circ \circ \circ$

Web Design

••000

Python

••000

Problem Solving Skills

••000

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

MAY 2022 - MAY 2023

Area Asset Protection Manager, Staples, Vancouver, BC

- Trained and developed management teams to enhance operational efficiency, leading to measurable improvements.
- Identified risks and minimized loss in partnership with management, ensuring customer and employee safety.
- Conducted and closed investigations into theft and fraud, reducing incidents significantly.

MAR 2015 - MAY 2022

Regional Loss Prevention Manager, Rexall Drugs, Vancouver, BC

- Developed and evaluated an online audit program, increasing completed audits and corrections by 200%.
- Conducted and closed investigations into theft and fraud, ensuring compliance and security.
- Implemented real-time action plans and notifications, enhancing audit efficiency and accountability.
- Streamlined team processes, boosting efficiency by 20% through take charge leadership.

MAR 2013 - MAR 2015

Field Investigator, Target, Vancouver, BC

- Trained Assets Protection teams on surveillance, case development, interviewing, and interventions.
- Led 18 stores to achieve top national results.
- Enhanced team skills in non-violent interventions and apprehensions.
- Implemented strategies that improved store security measures.
- Developed internal cases leading to significant reductions in losses.

JAN 2004 - MAR 2013

District Loss Prevention Manager, Best Buy, Vancouver, BC

- Trained managers in inventory control, boosting engagement and communication.
- Implemented shrinkage reduction strategies, enhancing store profitability.
- Developed training programs, improving managerial skills and store performance.
- Facilitated open communication, increasing team productivity.
- Conducted and closed theft and fraud investigations, ensuring store integrity.
- Elevated team performance by 20% through strategic workflow enhancements.

APR 2001 - JAN 2004

General Manger, Winners Merchants Inc., Vancouver, BC

- Led team of 5 managers and 85 staff, ensuring smooth daily operations and customer satisfaction.
- Increased profitability through efficient team management and operational improvements.
- Developed strategic plans to enhance service quality and operational efficiency.
- Resolved operational issues swiftly, maintaining high customer satisfaction.
- Achieved measurable results in team performance and customer feedback.

JavaScript Frameworks

• • 0 0 0

Developing APIs

••000

JUN 1990 - JAN 2001

District Manager, Bata Shoes & Athletes World, Vancouver, BC

- Managed 17 locations, leading 17 direct reports and 250+ team members across the province.
- Increased profitability and operational efficiency across all locations.
- Implemented strategic plans resulting in significant sales growth.
- Resolved complex operational issues, ensuring smooth business operations.
- Fostered a collaborative environment, enhancing team performance and customer satisfaction.
- · Transformed operational practices to enhance team synergy and productivity.
- Analyzed market trends to align operations with consumer demands.
- Led initiatives that significantly improved customer engagement.

EDUCATION

OCT 2023 - SEP 2024

Certified Web Developer, CareerFoundry, Berlin, Germany

CUSTOM SECTION

Meet App

WEB DEVELOPMENT PROJECT

Personal project, CareerFoundry, April 2023

- · Developed a progressive web application (responsive, cross platform, offline available and ability to add to home screen) using React.
- · Followed test-driven-development approach, translating user stories into scenarios for unit and integration testing (Jest), acceptance testing (Cucumber) and end-to-end testing (Puppeteer).
- · Implemented serverless functions (AWS Lambda) to authenticate & authorize users (OAuth).

The Movie App

WEB DEVELOPMENT PROJECT

Personal project, CareerFoundry, February 2023

- · Created a non-relational database (MongoDB) of top movies.
- · Built a REST API with Node.js and Express, using Mongoose to interact with the database.
- · Tested the API endpoints with Postman, wrote clean and concise documentation, deployed with Heroku.
- · Created single-page, responsive front-end application using React and Angular.